const easyQuestions = [
    {
        question : 'Which movie started the Marvel Cinematic universe?',
        1 : 'The Avengers',
        2 : 'Captain America: The First Avenger', 
        3 : 'Thor',
        4 : 'Iron Man', 
        correct : 'Iron Man'
    },
    {
        question : "What is the name of Thor's hammer?",
        1 : 'Mjolnir',
        2 : 'Storm breaker', 
        3 : 'Jonathan',
        4 : ' Gugnir', 
        correct : 'Mjolnir'
    },
    {
        question : 'What does the D in SHIELD stand for?',
        1 : 'Defense',
        2 : 'Division', 
        3 : 'Damage',
        4 : 'Department', 
        correct : 'Division'
    },
    {
        question : 'How many Avengers were there originally in the MCU?',
        1 : '6',
        2 : '7', 
        3 : '8',
        4 : '9', 
        correct : '6'
    },
    {
        question : 'Who is not considered an Avenger in the MCU?',
        1 : 'Spider-Man',
        2 : 'Black Widow', 
        3 : 'Black Panther',
        4 : 'Hulk', 
        correct : 'Black Panther'
    },
    {
        question : 'Who is related to Loki in the MCU',
        1 : 'Thor',
        2 : 'Bucky Barnes', 
        3 : 'Sylvie',
        4 : 'Bruce Banner', 
        correct : 'Thor'
    },
    {
        question : 'What is the name of the alien force that attacked New York in The Avengers?',
        1 : 'The Chitauri',
        2 : 'Black Order', 
        3 : 'Flag Smashers',
        4 : 'Hydra', 
        correct : 'The Chitauri'
    },
    {
        question : 'Which character was introduced for the first time in Captain America: Civil War?',
        1 : 'Hulk',
        2 : 'Batroc', 
        3 : 'Spider-Man',
        4 : 'The Falcon', 
        correct : 'Spider-Man'
    },
    {
        question : "Who is Peter Quill's father",
        1 : 'Yondu',
        2 : 'Ego', 
        3 : 'Kurt',
        4 : 'Odin', 
        correct : 'Ego'
    },
    {
        question : 'Who is the main villain in Thor:The Dark World?',
        1 : 'Loki',
        2 : 'Malekith', 
        3 : 'Gorr',
        4 : 'Eitri', 
        correct : 'Malekith'
    }
]

const mediumQuestions = [
    {
        question : "How many phases make up the infinity saga have?",
        1 : '2',
        2 : '3', 
        3 : '4',
        4 : '5', 
        correct : '3'
    },
    {
        question : "Which MCU TV show was released first?",
        1 : "WandaVision",
        2 : "Loki",
        3 : "Hawkeye",
        4 : "The Falcon and the Winter Soldier",
        correct : 'WandaVision'
    }, 
    {
        question : "Who is Loki's father?",
        1 : 'Odin',
        2 : 'Thanos', 
        3 : 'Dimitri',
        4 : 'Laufey', 
        correct : 'Laufey'
    }, 
    {
        question : "What is the name of the radical group that kidnaps Tony Stark when he was in Afghanistan?",
        1 : 'A.I.M',
        2 : 'Taliban', 
        3 : 'Ten Rings',
        4 : 'Black Tigers', 
        correct : 'Ten Rings'
    },
    {
        question : "What are the children of Thanos formally known as and how many members are there?",
        1 : 'Black Order ; 4',
        2 : 'Black Order ; 5', 
        3 : 'Sinister 6; 6',
        4 : 'Horsemen of Appocolypse; 4', 
        correct : 'Black Order ; 4'
    },
    {
        question : "Who hired the Guardians in Guardians of the Galaxy Vol.2?",
        1 : "Kree",
        2 : "Sovereign",
        3 : "Ravagers",
        4 : "Clandestines",
        correct : 'Sovereign'
    }, 
    {
        question : "Who found the Tesseract for SHIELD?",
        1 : "Nick Fury",
        2 : "Tony Stark",
        3 : "Howard Stark",
        4 : "Phil Coulson",
        correct : 'Howard Stark'
    },
    {
        question : "Who was the villain in Ant Man?",
        1 : "Ghost",
        2 : "Yellow Jacket",
        3 : "Hydra",
        4 : "Baskin-Robbins",
        correct : 'Yellow Jacket'
    },
    {
        question : "Who was not in Doctor Strange?",
        1 : "Mordo",
        2 : "Kaescillus",
        3 : "Clea",
        4 : "Ancient One",
        correct : 'Clea'
    },
    {
        question : "How many personalities does Moon Knight have?",
        1 : "1",
        2 : "2",
        3 : "3",
        4 : "4",
        correct : '3'
    }
]

const hardQuestions = [
    {
        question : "How many cameos had stan lee made in Marvel movies?",
        1 : "22",
        2 : "23",
        3 : "27",
        4 : "32",
        correct : '22'
    },
    {
        question : "Who wields the Gungnir in the MCU?",
        1 : "Hela",
        2 : "Loki",
        3 : "Odin",
        4 : "Sif",
        correct : 'Odin'
    },
    {
        question : "Who was the second person to create the super soldier serum?",
        1 : "Abraham skine",
        2 : "Bruce Banner",
        3 : "Jonathan Schmidt",
        4 : "Wilfred Nagel",
        correct : 'Wilfred Nagel'
    },
    {
        question : " What was the name of the secret project in Captain America:The Winter Soldier?",
        1 : "Project Strafish",
        2 : "Project Insight",
        3 : "Project Clean Slate",
        4 : "Project Obsidian",
        correct : 'Project Insight'
    },
    {
        question : "Who is Black Widow's father according to Red Skull?",
        1 : "Ivan",
        2 : "Alexei",
        3 : "Drakov",
        4 : "Anton",
        correct : 'Ivan'
    },
    {
        question : "What is the name of the primary AI used by Iron Man?",
        1 : "EDITH",
        2 : "FRIDAY",
        3 : "Veronica",
        4 : "Karen",
        correct : 'FRIDAY'
    }, 
    {
        question : "Who is the original prime Eternal?",
        1 : "Sersi",
        2 : "Ajax",
        3 : "Gilgamesh",
        4 : "Kingo",
        correct : 'Ajax'
    },
    {
        question : "What does Kilmonger do when he becomes the King in What IF?",
        1 : "Burn the purple herb garden",
        2 : "Declare war on the United States",
        3 : "Kill T'Challa",
        4 : "Kill Zuri",
        correct : 'Declare war on the United States' 
    },
    {
        question : "When do we first see Red Skull in the MCU?",
        1 : "Norway, 1942",
        2 : "Germany, 1947",
        3 : "Germany, 1942",
        4 : "Norway, 1947",
        correct : 'Norway, 1942' 
    },
    {
        question : "What kind of alien is Goose from Captain Marvel?",
        1 : "Rajaks",
        2 : "Flerken",
        3 : "Kallusians",
        4 : "Pluvians",
        correct : 'Flerken' 
    },
]
